// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q002: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Professional and amateur photographers ------ can participate in the annual photography contest, which takes place in October.',
      choices: ['alike', 'even', 'quite', 'enough'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['alike'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: '------ a recent government survey, annual income per household last year was about the same as it was five years ago.',
      choices: ['Additionally', 'Although', 'According to', 'As soon as'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['to'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Clarel Bookstore, located in the northern part of Wallaby City, will ------ host book signings for its members.',
      choices: ['occasions', 'occasion', 'occasionally', 'occasional'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['occasionally'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'A list of full------time job ------ at Canterbury Technology will be posted on the website tomorrow afternoon.',
      choices: ['open', 'openings', 'openly', 'opened'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['openings'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'The product developed by Orange Solutions was ------ in terms of design than that of Roseville System, but the price was about the same.',
      choices: ['sophisticated', 'most sophisticated', 'more sophisticated', 'sophisticate'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['sophisticated'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: '------ the tourist season begins, Trattoria Porte will extend its hours of operation until 23:00.',
      choices: ['Afterward', 'Prior to', 'Once', 'During'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Once'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: '------ the inclement weather, many residents came to the concert venue to listen to the performance by the renowned pianist.',
      choices: ['Despite', 'Although', 'Nevertheless', 'Whenever'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Despite'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Graden Consulting attempted to recruit a senior data analyst internally, but ------ employees met the job requirements.',
      choices: ['both', 'few', 'most', 'a lot of'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['few'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Due to poor sales, plans to close several branches in the Kansai region ------.',
      choices: ['considers', 'have been considering', 'was considered', 'are being considered'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['considered'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'With the implementation of a state------of------the------art customer management system, Taylor Bay Hotel has ------improved customer satisfaction.',
      choices: ['substantial', 'substantiate', 'substantiating', 'substantially'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['substantially（大いに）'],
      score: 1,
    },
  ],
}